hellouganda.com 2017-04-03

# Privacy Policy - Hello Uganda Services Ltd

Privacy Policy Guidelines  
privacy policy

Hellouganda Privacy Policy  
We understand that making purchases, bookings, downloads online involves a great deal of trust on  
your part. We take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security  
and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read the following policy to  
learn about our privacy practices. By visiting our website, www.Hellouganda.com, you are accepting the  
practices described herein.

What information we collect from you.  
How we use your information  
With whom we share your information.  
How you can access your information  
Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information.  
How we protect our information.  
Children’s privacy  
External links  
Changes to this privacy policy.  
How you can contact us

What information we collect from you  
Generally we receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. This includes information that can identify you (“personal information”), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal and e-mail addresses, and, in some cases, billing information (such as credit card number, cardholder name, and expiration date). We also may request information about your booking preferences, including room requests, seat selection, frequent flyer/hotel/car rental program information, and ticketing options. You can choose not to provide information to us, but in general some information about you is required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services;; participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes; ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on our site.

How we use your information  
Hellouganda.com uses sensitive billing information (such as cardholder name, credit card number, and expiration date) for the purpose of completing the travel purchases, hotel bookings, online payments you conduct on our site. We use other information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to provide you with travel, bookings, payments confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing travel, payment &,booking notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to measure interest in and improve our products,services, and Web site; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may  
be of interest to you; to otherwise customize your experience with Hellouganda.com; to reward you as part of any reward and recognition program you choose to join; to solicit information from you, including thorough surveys; to resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise  
described to you at the point of collection. Please review “Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information” below.

With whom we share your information  
Hellouganda.com may share your information with the following entities: Suppliers such as hotels, car rental companies, super markets, pharmacies, schools and clinics or activity providers, who fulfill your online reservations. Throughout Hellouganda.com, all services provided by a third-party supplier are described as such. We do not share your email address with these suppliers unless they need it to fulfill the transactions you have made on Hellouganda.com, and we restrict their use of this information to that purpose. We do not place limitations on our suppliers’ use or disclosure of your other personal information. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any supplier whose products you purchase through Hellouganda.com.  
Please note that these suppliers also may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about you or to facilitate your transactions.

Third Party Vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, including credit card processing,business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys or sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. These companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose.  
Business Partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will appear with ours. If you choose to access these optional services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners and recommend you evaluate their practices before deciding to  
provide your personal information.

We also may share your information:

In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.  
When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of Hellouganda.com, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements.  
In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information. We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors a Web site receives or what are the most popular business transactions. This information does not contain any personal information  
and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.

How you can access your information  
you can access your information at various points on the Hellouganda.com Web site. These include:

My account page on Hellouganda.com, where you can view, update, or change your personal information. On this page, you also can change your password; select to have an automatic password sign-in when logging on to Hellouganda.com.

You can close your Hellouganda.com account by selecting the Account Closure option. We will send you an e-mail confirming your request to close your account to the e-mail address contained in your member profile. Please note that after you close an account, you will not be able to sign in or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new account at any time. Please also note that we may retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes as well as  
for record keeping integrity.

Your choices with respect to collection and use of your information

As discussed above, you can choose not to provide us with any information, although it may be needed to make online l purchases or to take advantage of certain features offered on Hellouganda.com.  
When you register as a member on Hellouganda.com, you will be given a choice as to whether you want to receive e-mail messages from Hellouganda.com about special offers. As a registered Hellouganda.com member, you can modify your choice at any time on the my account page under the heading “E-mail settings.”Whether registered as a Hellouganda.com member or not, you also will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such e-mail we send. Please note that we reserve the right to send you other communications, including service announcements, administrative messages,  
and surveys relating either to your Hellouganda.com account or to your transactions on Hellouganda.com, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.  
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from Hellouganda.com, you will not be able to access portions of our site.

How we protect your information  
we want you to feel confident about using Hellouganda.com to plan and purchase your hotel rooms, electronic vouchers, down load music, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no Web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for  
permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information.

Children’s privacy  
Hellouganda.com does not carry transactions or other services for purchase by children. Should a child whom we know to be under 18 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.

External Links  
If any part of the Hellouganda.com Web site links you to other Web sites, those Web sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
Hellouganda.com may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our Web site.

How you can contact us  
If you have questions about either Privacy Policy (or any of our online transactions), please e-mail us using our contact Us form ([info@hellouganda.com](mailto:info@hellouganda.com)).  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 1, 2009.
